<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Happenings Intro on Seacoast Area Bicycle Riders</title>
    <link>/happenings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Happenings Intro on Seacoast Area Bicycle Riders</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/happenings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bicycle Friendly State Report Card - League of American Bicyclists</title>
      <link>/happenings/bicycle-friendly-state-report-card-league-of-american-bicyclists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/happenings/bicycle-friendly-state-report-card-league-of-american-bicyclists/</guid>
      <description>Every year the League of American Bicyclists issues each state a &amp;ldquo;Bicycle Friendly State&amp;rdquo; report card based on over 100 data points with input from state agencies and advocates. The 2019 report shows that out of 50 states, New Hampshire has slid down to a 36th place ranking and Maine to a 20th place ranking.
No surprise that both states earned a &amp;ldquo;D&amp;rdquo; in infrastructure and funding.
Join SABR&amp;rsquo;s advocacy committee by contacting Andy@seacoastbikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NEW BIKE/PED PATH ACROSS LITTLE BAY IS OPEN!</title>
      <link>/happenings/new-bike-ped-path-across-little-bay-is-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/happenings/new-bike-ped-path-across-little-bay-is-open/</guid>
      <description>The new path provides a safe route for bicycles and pedestrians across Little Bay, between Dover and Newington/Portsmouth.
This temporary Bike/Pedestrian pathway was constructed in response to many years of advocacy by SABR members to maintain bike/ped access during the reconstruction of the General Sullivan Bridge. NHDOT originally proposed a shuttle service, which SABR vehemently opposed. The emergency closure of the General Sullivan Bridge in September of 2018 necessitated NHDOT to develop a solution sooner than anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>